on the e4j status updates so just to
在e4j状态更新上，因此
quickly quickly recap if you've been if
快速回顾一下，如果你去过
you saw me in Ludwigsburg for example
你在路德维希堡见过我
these some of these slides will be
这些幻灯片中的一些将是
familiar but it was announced back at
熟悉，但在
JavaOne that Java EE is coming to the
Java EE即将面世的JavaOne
post foundation and by all means please
张贴基础，请务必
join the discussion that we fit a e4j -
加入我们适合e4j的讨论-
community at work it's a very active
工作中的社区非常活跃
mailing list with lots of very
邮件列表中有很多
passionate people so we're very happy to
热情的人，所以我们很高兴
welcome this technology to eclipse there
欢迎这项技术使它黯然失色
this community is looking for a more
这个社区正在寻找更多
open process better models for
为以下方面打开更好的模型
collaboration among between the
之间的合作
community and vendors and they are
社区和供应商，他们是
looking to the Eclipse Foundation to
期待Eclipse基金会
provide that this year is going to be
前提是今年将是
the year that that all the technology
那一年，所有的技术
moves over it's also going to be the
移动它也将是
year where we are going to create a new
我们将要创建新的一年
process at the consolidation for doing
合并过程
specs similar to what the JCB has been
类似于JCB的规格
doing in the past as well as creating a
过去所做的以及创造一个
new brand and name for what was formerly
以前的新品牌和名称
known as Java EE and so the lot of
被称为Java EE，所以很多
interest in getting this technology
有兴趣获得这项技术
moved over to eclipse as rapidly as we
像我们一样迅速地蚀过
can do it so where are we so easy for
可以做到，所以我们在哪里这么容易
Jake is the top-level project that is
杰克（Jake）是
going to be hosting this technology and
将托管这项技术，
the focus at the moment is entirely on
目前的重点完全放在
getting that established as a
建立一个
functioning open source project so back
运作中的开放原始码专案
in October the coast of the Florida
在十月的佛罗里达海岸
directors approved the top-level project
董事批准了顶层项目
charter we have two existing projects it
宪章，我们有两个现有项目
Clips like in Yas on the banana clips
像香蕉上的Yas一样的剪辑
Foundation for a while we move those
基础一段时间我们将那些
over to Iggy 4j there were nine initial
到Iggy 4j，最初有9个
projects proposed the final total is
项目建议的最终总金额为
going to be somewhere between 35 to 40
大约在35到40之间
new projects so you can imagine that
新项目，所以您可以想象
that's a that's onboarding a lot of new
那是一个新的东西
technology and use new source code new
技术和使用新的源代码新
committers the first nine projects have
前九个项目的提交者
been created and provisions
被创建和规定
I think two of them have actually got
我认为其中两个实际上已经
source code into them now and so we are
源代码到他们现在，所以我们
onboarding these projects as rapidly as
尽快启动这些项目
we can in the background there's been a
我们可以在后台有一个
bunch of legal work that's been going on
一堆正在进行的法律工作
to make all of this possible so we would
使所有这些成为可能，所以我们将
put an agreement in place for example
例如达成协议
with Oracle to transfer ownership of the
与Oracle一起转让所有权
names of the projects like GlassFish
GlassFish等项目的名称
Jersey and so on to the equation so
球衣等等的方程式
that's been completed and we're in the
那已经完成了，我们在
process of actually transferring that
实际转移的过程
the registrations of GlassFish around
GlassFish的注册信息
the world under the ownership of the
所有权下的世界
Eclipse Foundation while we're doing
我们正在做的Eclipse基金会
this as at the same time we have a
与此同时，我们有一个
community lead process to select a new
社区牵头流程以选择新的
brand to replace Java EE so there's
品牌来取代Java EE，因此
discussions going on about that today
今天对此进行的讨论
the the fee for JP MC has whittled it
JP MC的费用减少了
down to a short list of names based on
缩小到基于的简短名称列表
input from the community and we are
来自社区的意见，我们
going at this moment we are going
在这一刻我们要去
through trademark with you to see which
通过商标与您一起了解
of those names could be plausibly
这些名字中的可能是合理的
trademarks and around the world to to be
商标以及全世界
used as the new name next up is creating
用作下一个新名称的创建
a working group so for those who are new
一个工作小组，所以对于那些新来的人
to Eclipse working groups are the
Eclipse工作组是
mechanism that we create member led
我们创建成员领导的机制
governance around project community and
围绕项目社区进行治理
the goal is really to complement what's
目标是真正地补充什么
happening in the open-source projects
发生在开源项目中
with additional activities related to
与其他相关的活动
marketing and branding and so on and in
市场营销和品牌推广等等
this particular case there's going to be
在这种特殊情况下
some special and additional work that's
一些特殊的和额外的工作
going to be done around creating
将围绕创建完成
specifications creating this brand
创建这个品牌的规格
enforcing the brand through a
通过一个品牌来加强品牌
compatibility program so this is going
兼容性程序，所以这会
to be definitely a very important and I
绝对是非常重要的，而我
think quite prominent working group
认为相当杰出的工作组
within the Eclipse community these are
在Eclipse社区中，这些是
just some of the key principles and
只是一些关键原则，
assumptions that we're using to drive
我们用来驱动的假设
the creation of the working group and
建立工作组并
for that matter the the e4j project
为此，e4j项目
community
社区
so open-source rules of engagement apply
因此适用开放源代码参与规则
as you would expect compatibility has
如您所愿，兼容性
been a key to the set set historical
成为历史设定的关键
success of Java EE all along which is
Java EE的成功始终是
you know roughly twenty years of success
你知道大约二十年的成功
around Java EE technology so that's why
关于Java EE技术的，这就是为什么
compatibility will continue to be
兼容性将继续
important to this group and that will
对这个群体很重要，那将
drive a lot of the decisions and the
做出很多决定，
processes that we're going to be making
我们将要进行的流程
around the spec process for implementing
围绕规范流程实施
test kits and implementing reference
测试套件和实施参考
implementations to ensure compatibility
确保兼容性的实现
of independent implementations down the
的独立实现
road but really the reasons a big part
道路，但真正的原因很大一部分
of the reason why this java ee
这个java ee的原因
technology is coming to eclipse is
科技即将日蚀
around innovation and increasing the
围绕创新和增加
pace of innovation and sustainability
创新和可持续发展的步伐
and agility so those are really sort of
和敏捷性，所以这些真的
the three three main goals that we need
我们需要的三个三个主要目标
to execute on over the next couple of
在接下来的几个执行
years and so setting the working group
年，因此成立了工作组
up for success on those on those
为那些成功的人
attributes is going to be a big part of
属性将成为
what we have to do this this year so
今年我们要做的是
just try to talk a little bit about the
只是尝试谈一点
relationship between the working group
工作组之间的关系
and the name of their next may or may
以及下一个可能的名称
not be the name that's why it's in
不是这个名字的原因
quotes and I'm doing a little air quotes
引号，我在做一些空中引号
here as I'm talking is is that's the so
我在说的是这样
in terms of the working group what do
在工作组方面做什么
they do there so they're member-driven
他们在那里做，所以他们是会员驱动的
there's going to be a governance model
将会有一个治理模型
and around that governance model this is
围绕该治理模型，这是
going to be around paying a budget for
将围绕支付预算
the working group and and possibly extra
工作组，还有可能
dues for the working group to make sure
工作组应缴纳的费用
that they have funds which could be used
他们有可以使用的资金
to support their activities they're
支持他们的活动
going to have to define and and a dot
将必须定义和一个点
define adopt and implement the spec
定义采用并实施规范
process to replace the role of the JCP
取代JCP角色的过程
has has historically in doing Java EE
历史上曾经做过Java EE
specifications create an entirely new
规格创造了全新的
brand in the software industry market
软件行业市场中的品牌
that brand raise awareness about that
该品牌提高了对此的意识
brand and then use that brand
品牌，然后使用该品牌
clients and enforcement for the
客户和执法
compatibility and of course as part of
兼容性，当然是
that implement that provides specs under
提供规范的工具
a license that allows independent
允许独立的许可证
implementations on the open source IDE
开源IDE上的实现
forge a top-level project is developer
打造顶级项目是开发人员
driven so every project that eclipse is
驱动，所以每个月蚀项目
a self-governing meritocracy and they
一个自治的精英阶层，他们
really and that's definitely happening
真的，那肯定在发生
already with EE for Jake they're going
已经与EE for Jake合作了
to be building the open source code in
在构建开源代码
the tcks the license that's been
掌握已经获得的许可证
selected for this group is the EPL
为此组选择的是EPL
version 2 with the secondary license
具有辅助许可证的版本2
being enabled with the GPL version 2
已使用GPL版本2启用
plus class Pathak section so that's the
加上班级Pathak部分，这就是
license that's that's being used by this
所使用的许可证
group that's very similar to the
小组非常类似于
historic license of GlassFish and the
GlassFish和
other related projects which previously
以前的其他相关项目
were CDL and in GPL classpath exception
是CDL和GPL类路径异常
open source rules of engagement apply as
开源参与规则适用于
we talked about some meritocracy etc
我们谈到了一些精英管理等
were applied here and the goal again
在这里应用，目标又来了
really around agility rapid innovation
围绕敏捷快速创新
we haven't done the spec process yet but
我们尚未完成规范流程，但
the sort of a prioritized sumption is
优先选择的种类是
that we will be creating specs largely
我们将主要创建规格
using the open source processes that we
使用我们的开源流程
use for everything else at Eclipse and
用于Eclipse的其他所有功能
then with the idea that once a draft
然后想到一次草案
spec has been created by the by the
规范是由创建的
project on the Eee forge a side it would
在Eee上进行项目锻造的一面
be referred to the working group for
被转交给工作组
ratification and adoption and so all of
批准和采用等
the processes that we're talking about
我们正在谈论的过程
here are governed by the Eclipse
这是由Eclipse控制的
development process and the IP policy
开发过程和知识产权政策
just like every other open-source
就像其他开源一样
project at Eclipse so some key points
在Eclipse进行项目，因此一些关键点
and some of the things that in the first
以及第一件事
one here is I think you'd be one of the
我想你会成为其中之一
major cultural changes if you will
重大的文化变革
relative to the how Java EE has evolved
相对于Java EE的发展方式
in the past which is that were
过去是
consciously trying to change the culture
有意识地试图改变文化
to be code first rather than spec first
首先是代码而不是规范
you know
你懂
so the idea is that you know let's let's
所以这个想法是，你知道让我们
get developers to build working code and
让开发人员构建工作代码并
once they've demonstrated that it's
一旦他们证明了
working then then and only then do you
那时候工作，只有那样你
do you work on this Factory so these are
你在这家工厂工作吗？
the three attributes of the spec process
规范流程的三个属性
that the JCP has always been you know a
JCP一直是你知道的
spec you have a TCK and you have a
规范，你有一个TCK，你有一个
reference implementation the going in
参考实施
assumption is that that will continue to
假设那将继续
be the case we've had numerous
事实是我们有无数
discussions about that with some key
一些关键的讨论
stakeholders in the Java EE ecosystem
EE生态系统中的利益相关者
and the consensus is that yes they still
共识是，他们仍然
want to continue with this so
想继续这样
compatibility still matters very very
兼容性仍然非常重要
much but on the other hand one of the
很多，但另一方面
major differences on the spec process is
规范流程的主要区别是
in the current JCP process there's a
在当前的JCP流程中，
notion of a spat lead who is a very
一个非常有力的争锋的概念
powerful entity in the indie spec
独立规范中的强大实体
process and actually ends up owning all
过程，实际上最终拥有所有
of the IP that's involved with that spec
该规范所涉及的IP
and that's not going to be the way we go
那不是我们要走的路
with the new spec process so this is
新的规范流程，所以这是
about lighter weight processes for specs
关于规格的轻量化工艺
and defining profiles and the like and
并定义配置文件等
really the goal of this group is to
这个小组的目标是
increase the pace of innovation and help
加快创新步伐并提供帮助
bring what we used to call or used to
带上我们曾经打电话或用来
think of as Enterprise Java to a cloud
视为企业Java到云端
native future so this is definitely
本地的未来，所以这绝对是
about the future not just about the
关于未来不只是关于
legacy
遗产